（忆往昔）
「被纯种头四代子孙
"Werewolves that are turned up to four generations.
所转化的狼人…
from pureblood…"
相对温和 并且可以在
"…are less feral and can transform before,
任何时候变形「
during, and after the lunar cycle."
白天是人类
A human by day,
夜晚月光下则是杀戮机器
a freak animal killing machine by moonlight.
狼人都很厉害
I mean, werewolves are badass.
但最棒的事是
Best part about it is,
我们已经知道要如何杀死这些混蛋
we already know how to bring these suckers down.
用这个直射心脏
One of these bad boys right to the heart.
迪恩是恶魔
Dean is a demon.
我不知道你是怎么做到的
I don't know how you did this,
我不知道你玩的是什么黑魔法
what kind of… black-magic stunt you pulled,
但你给我听好了 我会救回我哥哥的
but hear me … I will save my brother.
至死方休
or die trying.
住手 结束了
Stop. It's over.
和你的堕落没什么区别
I turned into to what you already are.
这话什么意思
And what exactly is that supposed to mean?
我知道你去找我的时候做了什么
I know what you did when you went looking for me.
我们俩究竟谁是魔头
…which one of us is really a monster?
你可能比我还烂
You might actually be worse than me.
我们血还多着呢
Look, we got a whole bunch more of these to go.
你可以让自己好过一点
You could make it a lot easier on yourself.
我们到底在干什么 小卡
What the hell are we doing to him, Cass?
净化血仪式是我知道的唯一办法
The ritual of purified blood is the only treatment I know.
你们看起来很担心
You look worried, fellas.
欢迎回来 迪恩
Welcome back, Dean.
也许你该先休息一阵
Hey, maybe you should, um…take some time.
恢复一下 再投入工作
before you get back to work … allow yourself to heal.
（如今）
（华盛顿州 打拉谟）
你真合我心意
Damn. Girl after my own heart.
要的就是你的心
That's the idea, sweetie.
怎么回事
What the hell?
[邪恶力量 第10季第4集]
我有话要问你
Hey, something I needed to ask you.
问吧
Shoot.
你经受过…
You've been…
踢伤 咬伤 抓伤
kicked, bit, scratched,
捅伤 附身 被杀死
stabbed, possessed, killed…
现在居然把胳膊肘扭了
And you sprain your friggin' elbow?
不只是扭伤那么简单
Dude, it was more than a sprain. All right?
而且对方是个恶魔啊 但是…
And it was a friggin' demon, but…
怎么了
But what?
怎么 打个吊带还成哭鼻子小妞了
That sling come with a slice of crybaby pie on the side?
得了吧
Please.
你还好吗
How you doing?
好极了
Golden, man.
得了
Come on.
真的 我挺好
Seriously, I'm good.
真的
I am.
我们…
You know, we got…
后备箱里有三箱冰啤
three more cases of this stuff on ice in the trunk.
一起休息一下
Taking some "we time."
这是我们最好的决定了
Best decision we ever made.
说得好
Here that.
看到今早报纸的报道了吗
See that thing in the paper this morning?
可能是动物袭击吧
Maybe it was an animal kill.
一座小镇上
It was three kills,
过去一个月内发生三起杀人案件
and it was in the Same town, all within the last month.
是啊
Yeah, you're right.
我们该打电话找人 叫他们去看看
We should call some guys, have 'em fix it.
- 嗯 有理 - 说定了
- Good. Smart. - Done.
或者
Or…
我们速战速决
We could be in and out.
- 就像送牛奶一样简单 - 是啊
- It's a milk run. - Right,
因为从来都不会这么简单
because that happens never.
萨姆 我们这么休假
Look, Sam, what we're doing here,
是挺好
it's good, okay?
我们一起闲待着
You and me hanging out.
但我需要工作
But I need to work.
我需要去查案
I need this.
如果出了岔子
If things go sideways…
哪怕是一点差错
I mean, like, an inch,
你必须告诉我一声
you gotta give me the heads-up.
没问题
Done.
我保证
You got my word.
（国王镇警局）
二位
Gentlemen.
我就不逞强了
Well, I'm not gonna lie.
你们能来我们太开心了
We're damn glad to see you.
你们肯定经常遇到这种事吧
You boys must come up on stuff like this all the time.
- 是啊 - 是啊
- Oh, yeah. - Oh, yeah.
没错
Yeah, definitely.
我在游戏室里见过浣熊 熊跑进游泳池
Hell, seen raccoons in rec rooms and bears in swimming pools.
但这个 你们说呢
But this? You tell me.
是啊
Yeah.
真是…
Oh. Well, uh…
从何说起啊
Where do we start?
又是…伐木
What with, uh…logging.
冰盖
Ice caps.
比特币什么的
Bitcoin. Yeah.
奥巴马啊
Obama.
那个 或许
You know what? Maybe…
或许你可以跟我们讲讲袭击的事
Maybe, uh, you could walk us through the attacks.
相似之处或异常之处
Any similarities, anything weird.
唯一的异常之处就是它们的相似之处
Only thing weird about them was how similar they were.
全都是被撕开个口子
Folks torn clean through.
心脏不见了
Hearts absent.
心脏不见是说
Hearts absent as in…
应该是被吃了
Consumed, most likely.
没有目击证人吗
And there were no witnesses?
镇广场和停车场的袭击
Well, the town square attack, the parking lot…
当时都很晚了 但酒吧那起
those were real late. But the bar?
那里人满为患
Hell, with how jammed the place was,
按理说总该有除了汤米之外的人看到什么啊
you'd think somebody other than Tommy would've seen something.
- 他看到了什么 - 不多
- And what did he see? - Honestly, not much.
汤米不是一个特别可靠的目击证人
Now Tommy ain't exactly what we call a reliable witness.
他逢人便说
And he's telling anybody who'll listen.
他看见个姑娘跟巴克一起去了后边
he saw some girl go out back with Barker,
还说她也被撕碎了
and she got torn up, too.
那么还有一名被害人喽
So there was a second victim?
是啊
Well, sure…
但汤米是个酒鬼
expect Tommy's a drunk.
而且没有尸体 DNA或血迹
There's no body, no D.N.A., no blood trail,
能证明他的说法
no nothing to suggest that.
- 稍等一下 - 嗯
- Give me one sec. - Yeah.
心脏不见 听上去是狼人
Hearts missing. Sounds wolfy to me, right?
即使就狼人来说 也够大胆的了
Pretty brazen, even for a werewolf.
你觉得是个女人吗
You think it was the girl?
去查查吧
Let's find out.
是啊 我和巴克一起
Yeah, Barker and I have been raising hell,
疯狂玩乐 追女人 骑摩托 很久了
chasing tail, and riding for a long time.
他一直知道 等他死的那天
Part of him always knew when his clock ran out,
会很不好看
it wasn't gonna be pretty.
但那样死去 被动物咬死
To go out like that? By some animal?
这太可怕了
Just ain't right.
能跟我们说说是怎么回事吗
You mind, uh, you mind telling us what went down?
只是像平时那样寻开心
It was just another party, you know?
巴克去了后面 没过多久
Barker went out back. The next thing you know,
大家就都喊叫成一片
everyone's yelling and screaming,
- 他被撕成了碎片 - 警长提到
- and he's all torn up. - Now the sheriff mentioned.
你觉得当时还有个姑娘
You thought there might've been a girl involved.
你觉得她也被杀了吗
You think she was killed, too?
没有
Nope.
没有什么女孩吗
So there was no girl?
说不好
Couldn't say.
我们不是警察 你懂吧
You know we're not cops, right?
执法人员都一样
Badge is a badge.
你要知道 因为我们常年在外工作
Well, you should also know that working outdoors the way we do,
我们见过不少诡异的东西
we see some… some pretty weird crap.
一些无法解释的东西
Stuff that we can't explain.
半数的事
I mean, hell, half the stuff,
我们如果不是一起经历了 自己都不会相信
we wouldn't have believed it ourselves had we not seen it together.
但你不住在这镇上
Well, you don't have to live in this town, mister.
你不用面对大家的嘲笑
You don't have to deal with the ridicule.
我只是想说 你看到的疯狂可能没那么疯狂
I'm just saying that crazy might not be half as crazy as you think.
那么如果有人说他看见了鬼
So if someone were to tell you they saw a ghost,
你会信吗
you'd…believe that?
你就当我们什么都信吧
Just assume we believe everything.
好吧
Okay, then.
那天晚上 我驾车经过斯特奇斯农场
The other night, I was taking a ride past the old Sturges farm.
回忆我跟巴克以前一起骑车出去的事
You know, thinking about the rides me and Barker used to go on.
我看到了她
I saw her, man.
谁
Saw her who?
那个姑娘
The girl.
- 在袭击之后吗 - 是的
- What, after the attack? - Hell, yeah.
她浑身是血地站在那儿 看着我
She was just standing there, all bloody, watching me.
所以我赶紧掉头回去了
So… so I turn the hell around, I-I ran back, thinking,
心想她是受伤了还是怎么的
damn, you know, she… she's hurt or something.
但她已经没影了
But…she was just gone.
消失不见了
Like, gone.
像鬼一样
Like a ghost.
我不在乎警察怎么说
No, I don't give one red cent in hell what the cops say.
我看到她了 她被吃了
She was there. She was eaten.
她就是个鬼
She's a freakin' ghost.
鬼可不会把人撕成碎片
Ghosts don't shred people like that.
是啊
Yeah, well…
看这破地方的样子 她还没完事呢
This flea bag, looks like she ain't done.
还想继续吃机车党
chowing down on sons of anarchy just yet.
看来她喜欢坏小子
Guess she likes bad boys.
那我们就去招呼招呼她吧
Well, wait'll she gets a load of us.
别再不接我电话了
Stop ignoring my calls.
马上拿起电话打给我
Pick up the phone and call me right now.
事情不该是这样的
This isn't how it's supposed to go.
我以前经历过这些 我不想…
Look, I've been down this road before and I'm not going to…
怎么了
What?
凯特
Kate?
我知道你们是谁
I know who you are.
恭喜
Congratulations.
学校的事之后 我以为你们会放过我
After what happened at school, I thought you'd let me go.
是啊 但那是在你开始杀人之前
Yeah, well, that was before you started dropping bodies.
- 什么 - 酒吧那人看到你了
- What? - Guy at the bar saw you.
就在你把他哥们撕碎之前
before you went all wolverine on his buddy.
所以 惊喜
So…surprise.
我们来了
Here we are.
凯特 你说你不会伤人的
Kate, you said you were gonna go straight.
怎么回事
What happened?
我变了
I guess things change.
我现在这样子…
Being this…
我也想支撑住 但渴望感太强烈了
I tried to be strong, but the hunger was too much.
太痛苦了
Too hard.
又没人给过我狼人速成教程
It's not like anyone gave me a handbook on how to be a werewolf.
看上去你目前为止做得还不错
Looks like you're doing a pretty good job so far.
撕碎别人的心 然后吃掉
Break some hearts, then you eat 'em.
我只有自己
I was on my own.
我…进化了
I…evolved.
你管杀无辜者叫进化
So that's what you call killing innocent people?
不管你们想怎么样 动手吧
Whatever you're gonna do, just…do it.
我说
You know what?
还是我来吧
Let me do it.
为什么
Why?
因为
Because…
我觉得你这次还是别插手了
I think you should sit this one out.
- 你说什么呢 - 你还没准备好 迪恩
- What are you talking about? - You're not ready, Dean.
喂
Hello?
沃顿 高中体育馆这边又发生一起动物袭人
Warden, we had another animal attack over at the high school gymnasium.
一个保安
Guy was a security guard.
跟前三起案件作案手法一样
Same M.O. as the other three.
- 什么时候 - 到场警官称
- When? - Deputy said the victim's blood.
他赶到时死者的血还有余温
was still warm when he got there,
肯定是一小时内的事
so had to be less than an hour ago.
好的 谢谢 再联系
Of course. Thank you. Um, I'll be in touch.
我们有麻烦了
We got a problem.
除了那个芭比狼人吗
What, besides, uh, werewolf barbie over here?
是的
Yeah.
天黑之前 镇那边发生了另一起案件
There was another kill, across town, just before dark.
凯特怎么杀完人又赶回来…
Well, how did Kate get her murder on and then get back here b…
- 你觉得不是她 - 我说不好
- You don't think she did it. - Look… I don't know, man.
但就我看来
But as far as I'm concerned…
该死
Damn it!
好吧 如果不是她在杀人
All right, if she's not icing people,
那何必扮坏人
then why play the big bad wolf?
或许她是跟狼群一起行动
Maybe she's running with a pack?
想保护他们
You know, trying to protect them?
那是多大的代价
Well, a hell of a price to pay.
她刚刚差点就没命了
She was about two seconds away from taking a dirt nap.
- 那是什么 - 她的手机
- What is that? - It's her phone.
看看我们来之前她是在给谁打电话
Let's see who she was booty calling when we pulled up.
感谢致电林肯汽车旅馆
Thank you for calling the Lincoln Motel.
有什么可以帮您的吗
Can I help you?
你刚刚说什么我没准备好是怎么回事
So what's this about me not being ready back there?
我不是想跟你吵架什么的 迪恩
I'm… I wasn't… trying to start something, Dean.
我只是说 我以为我们休假
I was just saying, I thought that was the whole point.
就是为了这个
of us taking a break. You know?
没事 我懂的
Oh, no. No, yeah. I get that.
这没什么
And, you know, there's no worries there.
好吧
Okay.
但我得问问 你呢
But I gotta ask. What about you?
我怎么了
What about me, what?
你准备好了吗
Are you ready?
我有什么准备不好的
Why wouldn't I be ready?
莱斯特
Lester.
Lester?
我老婆把我赶走了
My wife kicked me to the curb.
我们都4个月没做爱了
We haven't had sex for four months,
不过她可是没少做
but not that she hasn't been having plenty.
你或许是可以复仇的
It is possible that you can have your revenge.
谁召唤我 什么目的
Who summons me, and for what purpose?
莱斯特 别
Lester! Don't!
杀了我妻子 我的灵魂就归你了
Kill my wife, and my soul is yours.
你是谁
Who are you?
你还是恶魔呢
You're a punk-ass demon!
你现在要为我工作
And you work for me now.
你真的要扯上莱斯特
You're serious? This is about Lester?
别误会 我不是…
Um, don't get me wrong. I'm not… I'm not…
我也不是想跟你吵架什么的
I'm not trying to start anything either, okay?
我只是说 或许我们该谈谈这事
I'm just saying, maybe… maybe we oughta talk about that.
好吧 但是这没什么好谈的
Okay, expect there's nothing to talk about.
好吧
Okay.
我只是觉得 既然我们要坦诚相待
I just figured, since we're opening up veins.
那或许你该谈谈那个被你鼓动得去
that maybe you'd want to talk about the guy.
卖灵魂的人
who you made sell his soul.
是你杀了他
The guy who you then killed, right?
我们是在说同一个人吧
I mean, that's the same guy we're talking about?
我当时是个恶魔
I was a demon.
是嘛 我没发现呢
Oh, you were a demon? Oh, I didn't realize that.
莱斯特迟早要付出出卖灵魂的代价
Hey, man, Lester was gonna pay for that soul shake sooner or later.
所以说 这事还是得怪你
So technically, it's still on you.
你要我说什么啊 迪恩
What do you want from me, Dean? Look, I w…
我也不愿事情变成这样 但我当时得找到你
I'm not happy about it, okay? But I needed to find you.
所以如果我
So if I had to…
不得不打破些规矩
bend a few rules…
- 黑化 - 黑化 好吧
- Go dark. - Go dark. Sure.
随你怎么说吧
Label it if you want.
我再说一遍 我没埋怨你的意思
Look, man, again, I'm not complaining, okay?
事实上 恰恰相反
In fact, I'm doing just the opposite of complaining. I…
我只是…
I just…
又是莱斯特 还有其他那些…
You know, between Lester and the others…
没有其他人了
There weren't others.
好吧 不管怎样
Okay, either way,
或许我们两个都需要休假
maybe we both needed that time off.
这挺好 聊聊挺好
This is good. This is good.
嗯 好吧
Yeah. Okay.
前台说
All right, so the, uh, clerk says.
一个金发女孩黎明前入住了3号房
a blonde rolled into room 3 just before sunup.
- 一个人吗 - 他觉得是的
- She alone? - He thinks so.
她出来了
She's on the move.
她干什么
What's she doing?
找早餐
Looking for breakfast.
凯特
Kate!
结束了
It's over.
天呐
Oh, god.
求你们 别杀我 你们要什么都行
Please, don't. I'll give you anything you want.
凯特呢
Where's Kate?
谁
Who?
你刚刚从她的旅馆房间出来
You were just in her motel room.
什么 那是我的房间
What? That's my room.
你为什么跟踪那人
Why were you following that guy?
罗比吗 我认识他
Robbie? I-I know him.
我只是想吓唬他一下
I just wanted to surprise him.
试试她
Test her.
试我什么
Test me for what?
不要
No!
救命 谁救救我
Help! Somebody me help!
别紧张
Just take it easy.
我不想死
I don't want to die.
住手
Stop it! Stop it!
别
Don't!
她是我妹妹
She's my sister.
跟丢了
I lost her.
凯特 你妹妹为什么是狼人
Kate, why is your sister a werewolf, huh?
- 说 - 迪恩 让她说话
- Why?! - Dean. Let her talk.
- 我就是让她说 - 那就把枪放下
- I am! - Then put the gun down.
凭什么 让她再跑一次吗
Why? So she can run again? Nuh-uh.
她刚刚救了我们
She just saved our lives.
我妹妹是狼人是因为我转化了她
My sister is a werewolf because I turned her into one.
你现在应该想办法为自己开脱才对
Okay, this is the part where you help yourself out.
我不管 我受够了谎言
I-I don't care. All right? I'm sick of the lies.
我问问明白
Let me get this straight.
我们可怜你 所以让你逃跑了
We let you run because we take pity on you,
结果你却到处转化人吗
and you turn around and you start making pups?
还杀人
You start killing people?!
不是的 我不是杀人犯
It's not like that! I'm no killer.
我可记得你留给我们的那部小电影里
Well, the way I remember it from the snuff film that you left us,
记录了你杀了你男友的好哥们
is that you killed your boyfriend's best friend.
那是因为布莱恩发疯了
That's because Brian went crazy.
我别无选择
I had no other choice.
好吧 凯特 如果不是你
Okay, Kate, if this wasn't you…
这可很不好说
That's a big "if."
那是谁干的
Then who was it?
你妹妹吗
Your sister?
是你妹妹干的吗 凯特
Your sister do this, Kate?
不是吧
Really?
你差点为她挨了子弹 什么都不肯说吗
You almost took a bullet for her, and you got nothing?
你指望我说什么
What do you want me to say?
- 实话 - 伙计们
- The truth! - Hey, guys.
我们能去别处聊吗
Can we, uh, take it somewhere else?
是啊 我们去喝杯咖啡
Oh, yeah, sure. Go grab some coffee,
来点「熊心」
maybe some bear hearts.
去好好玩吧
Let's party.
要知道
Just so you know,
因为布莱恩 我一直带着这个
Brian's the reason I carry this.
我只是想给你看样东西
I'm just showing you something.
如果我像布莱恩那样发狂
In case I ever lose it, like Brian did,
不用你们来杀了我
you won't have to kill me.
说起来容易做起来难
Yeah, well, saying it and doing it are two different things.
我是认真的
I'm serious.
不管你们信不信
And whether you believe me or not,
我从未伤害过真正无辜的人
I've never hurt anyone who didn't deserve it.
我也从没吃过人心
And I have never, ever eaten a human heart.
怪不得谷仓那里那么多死鸡
Guess that explains all the dead chickens back at the barn.
我能找到什么吃什么
I eat what I can find,
希望大家不会在意那些
what people won't miss, hopefully.
小动物 鹿
Small game, deer.
我冥想
I meditate.
瑜伽也有帮助
Yoga helps.
瑜伽
Yoga?
好吧
Okay.
随你笑吧
You laugh, but…
但我愿尝试一切方法
I'll pretty much try anything.
控制好我的那一面
to keep that side of me under control.
这真好啊 凯特
Well, that is great, Kate.
真的
It really is.
而且我很高兴
And it's nice to see that, uh, this.
这种嬉皮士新时代生活方式
hippie-dippie new age crap has had such.
对你妹妹有这么积极的影响
a positive influence over your sister.
塔莎
Tasha…
她不一样
She's a different story.
我离开学校之后
After I left school, I was…
我漂泊不定
adrift.
十分迷茫
Lost.
不知道
Not really sure.
我该去哪
where to go or…
该怎么办
What to do, so…
于是我去了一个安全的地方
I went someplace safe.
我回了家
I went home.
但是 虽然我不会伤人
But…even though I'd be good,
我还是得为我家人考虑
I started to think about my family.
他们能安全吗
How safe were they going to be?
我是狼人
I was a werewolf.
再说还有你们
And then, of course, there was you two.
如果你们跑来杀我呢
What if you showed up and tried to kill me?
我不能冒这险
I couldn't risk that.
于是
So I…
我离开了
Walked away.
再没打电话 或者写信
Never called, never wrote,
就那么…
Just…
开始了新生活
started a new life.
直到一天 我看到了我妹妹脸书上发布的新消息
Until one day, I saw a posting on my sister's facebook page.
塔莎遭遇了严重的车祸
Tasha had been in a really bad car accident.
医生认为她是活不下来了
The doctors didn't think she was gonna make it.
我们一向很亲密
We were always so close,
所以
so…
我得去道别
I had to go say good-bye.
然后
Then…
我突然想到
it hit me.
我的这个诅咒
This curse that I had,
这个给我带来无限痛苦和折磨的诅咒
that had brought me nothing but pain and suffering,
或许终于能做件好事了
could actually finally maybe do something good.
如果我把塔莎转化成狼人
If I turned tasha into a werewolf,
她的伤口就能治愈 她的命就能保住
it would heal her wounds, save her life,
她将拥有第二次机会
give her a second chance.
所以
So, uh…
我做了不可想象的事
I did the unthinkable.
一开始 我以为我失败了
At first, I thought I'd failed,
即使狼人自愈很快
that… even though werewolves heal quickly,
对塔莎而言也太迟了
it was too late for Tasha.
然后她醒了
Then she woke up,
病好了 看起来挺不错
not sick anymore, but okay.
塔莎有许多疑问
Tasha had so many questions.
发生了什么 她怎么到这里来的
What happened? How did she get here?
所以…
So…
我就和她直说了
I was straight with her.
好的 坏的 丑恶的
The good, the bad, the ugly.
我们是什么
What we were.
以及我们永远也不能回家的原因
and why we could never go back home,
以及我们必须控制自己 这是我们的责任
and the responsibility we had to control what we'd become.
我是从医院把你接来的
I picked you up from the hospital.
我会带你去一个安全的地方 好吗
I'm gonna take you someplace safe, okay?
接受这些很不容易
It was a lot to swallow.
但我们拥有彼此
But we had each other,
我当时觉得这就够了
and that felt like enough.
至少我是这么以为
Or…so I thought.
我妹妹
My sister,
她向我警告她不要做的一切屈服了
she gave in to everything that I had warned her about.
而且…
And…
我知道
I knew,
即使那时我不愿承认…
even if I couldn't bring myself to admit it then…
我知道我在失去她
I knew I was losing her.
所以当时在谷仓
So back at the barn,
那都是为了保护塔莎而演的戏吗
that was all just an act to protect Tasha?
她是我的亲人
She's family.
所以 没错 她值得我为她送命
And, yeah, worth eating a bullet for.
而且如今她比以往都更需要我
And she needs me now more than ever.
这是我惹得的乱子 我必须解决
This is my mess. I gotta clean it up.
那你打算怎么做呢 凯特
And how do you plan on doing that, Kate?
带塔莎离开这里
By getting Tasha out of here.
她一直都没听你的话
She hasn't listened to you yet.
你凭什么认为她现在会开始听话
Why do you think she's gonna start now?
我不知道 但是…
I don't know, but…
我必须得试试
I've gotta try.
我们会去深林
Y-you know, we'll go out into the woods.
远离人群 无论多久
We'll drop out for however long it takes.
直到她学会控制自己
until she learns to control this.
现在才知道团建 有点晚了 不觉得吗
Little late for team building, don't you think?
那又怎样
So, what?
我就抛弃她吗
I just abandon her?
这是我做的
I did this.
我欠她一个纠正过错的机会
I owe her every chance to make it right.
假如她永远也改正不了呢
What if she never does?
那我会自己处理
Then I'll take care of it.
你会处理
You'll take care of it?
你知道这意味着什么吗
You know what that means?
你可以去问问布莱恩
Why don't you ask Brian?
说不定不用到那一步
Well, maybe it doesn't have to come to that.
假如你一开始就对我们坦白
You know, if you had shot straight with us from the get-go,
我们也许早就可以帮助你了
we might've been able to help you a lot sooner.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我们可以治愈你们两个
By curing you both.
算了吧
Shut up.
好吧 不用谢
Yeah, okay, or you're welcome.
狼人是治愈不了的
There is no cure for werewolves.
很长一段时间以来 的确如此
And for a long time, that was true,
但是我们找到一个办法
but we found one.
我们这边需要的东西都有了
Now we've got everything we need on our end.
明白吗 不过时间不等人
Okay? But the clock is tickin',
我们还需要一样东西 塔莎
and we need one more thing… Tasha.
除非你想自己来
Unless you wanna do this without her.
不 不
N-no. No.
路程挺远 不过
It's a long drive, but…
我知道去哪找她
I know where to find her.
你干什么 根本没有解药的
Dude, what are you doing? There is no cure.
有
There's one.
迪恩 这事没那么简单
Dean, it's a little more complicated than that.
凯特和塔莎都是怪物 明白吗
Kate and Tasha are monsters, okay?
据我所知 我们是要杀怪物的
Last I checked, we kill monsters.
对 可凯特是在为她妹妹争取
Right, but how can you possibly blame Kate.
你怎么能怪她 我们不也总这样吗
for fighting for her sister? We do it all the time.
是啊 咱们的结果可好得很呢
Well, yeah, and that's worked wonders for us.
至少我们还在 不是吗
Well, we're still here, aren't we?
是啊 但这样对吗
Yeah, but is it right?
你为我做了那么多 这血印还是去不掉
I mean, all that you've done for me, I've still got this mark.
我们会想到办法的 总有办法的
And we'll figure that out. We always do.
可你不能把我们的遭遇
But you can't take whatever's happened to us.
或者说你的遭遇
or to you and…
强加给这两个姑娘
and dump it at these girls' feet.
好吧 怎么 你想区别对待这事
All right, so, what? You wanna nuance this thing?
说吧 有什么计划
Hit me. What's your plan?
凯特
Kate?
她睡着了
She's out.
好吧 那么
Okay. Then, um…
有点事我得告诉你 我…
I gotta tell you something. I, uh…
- 莱斯特的事我说谎了 - 什么
- I lied about Lester. - What?
确实还有其他人
There were others.
- 其他人类 - 不不不 我…
- Other humans? - No. No, no. And…
我应该还伤了几个猎人
and I'm sure there were a few hunters I rubbed…
或者说是揍了
or I…punched the wrong way,
不过…不
But…no.
我把最狠的招都留给坏人了
I pretty much saved my best stuff for the bad guys.
但你得明白 迪恩
But you gotta understand something, Dean.
我看着你死了
I watched you die.
我扛着你
And I carried you.
我把你的尸体扛回了房间
I carried your corpse into your room,
还把你放到了床上
and I put your dead body on your bed,
然后你就…
and then you just…
嗯
Yeah.
- 是啊 - 我明白
- Yeah. - I know.
我可能是希望那字条能让你明白
I guess I was hoping that note would, you know, fill in the blanks.
那张「别找我」的字条吗
"Don't look for me"? That note?
还真是太有用了 多谢你留了条
Yeah, that was really informative. Thanks.
我…
Yeah. I…
怎么了
What?
说来挺丢人的
It's embarrassing, you know?
- 什么丢人 - 一切
- W-what's embarrassing? - All of it.
就是 字条啊
You know, the… the… that note.
克劳力啊
Crowley.
一切
Everything.
迪恩 你当时是恶魔
Dean, you were a demon.
是吗 多谢了 我还没发现呢
I was a demon? Oh, thanks. I didn't… I didn't realize.
得了吧
Shut up.
而且 我还没说「谢谢」
Not to mention, I never even said "Thank you""
所以
So…
你永远不用说那俩字 起码对我不用
You don't ever have to say that, not to me.
好吧…
Well…
很好 那我看…
Good. Then I guess…
这就算没问题了吧
guess it's all gravy.
小憩一下就回归正轨
Little r and r and we are back at it.
怎么样了
How we doing?
越来越近了
We're getting close.
这是什么地方
What is this place?
我和塔莎从小时候
Ever since Tasha and I were little,
就总跟父母来这个小屋
we've been coming up to this cabin with our parents.
为什么你觉得塔莎会在这里
Now why do you think Tasha will even be here?
她变成狼人后 我们知道会很艰难
When she became a wolf, we knew it was gonna be hard,
所以我们想了一个万一出了岔子的逃离计划
so we kinda came up with this escape plan in case things ever got bad.
这里是个汇合点吗
So it's a rendezvous spot?
差不多
Pretty much.
现在怎么办
Now what?
也许应该让我先进去 跟她解释清楚
Maybe I should go in first, explain all this?
好主意
Sounds good.
你在干什么
What are you doing?!
你这个混蛋
You son of a bitch!
根本没有治愈方法 对吧
There is no cure, is there?
亏我相信你
I trusted you.
这不是她的错
It's not her fault.
是我的
It's mine.
- 她杀了人 - 因为我转化了她
- She killed people. - Because I did this to her, okay?
所以如果你们要讨债 冲我来
So if you want your pound of flesh, take me.
我们一会儿再处理你
We'll deal with you later.
- 但她可以得到拯救 - 不可能
- But she can be saved! - No.
塔莎陷得太深
Tasha's in too deep.
不可能再好转了
You don't ever come back from that,
绝不可能
not ever.
来吧 萨姆
Come on, Sammy.
不
No!
求你们 别这样
Please! Don't do this!
不要
Don't!
求你了 萨姆
Please, Sam!
求你们了
Please don't!
真不敢相信我的亲姐姐背叛了我
I can't believe my own sister betrayed me.
是吗 不过…她并没有
Yeah, except… she didn't.
你不会开枪的
You're not gonna shoot me.
为什么
And why is that?
萨姆
Sam.
放下枪 不然这位万人迷的脑袋就要开花了
Drop the gun, or dreamboat here gets his mind blown.
别听她的 萨姆
Don't do it, Sam.
怎么样…萨姆
Well… Sammy?
塔莎
Tasha!
你在…这些人是谁
What did … who are these people?
布兰顿 崔维斯
Brandon. Travis.
我转化了他们
I turned them.
他们是我们的新家人
They're our new family.
是啊 可真是个标准的疯子家族
Yeah, you're a regular psycho Brady Bunch.
别
No!
你对男生的品味一向很烂
You've always had crappy taste in guys.
塔莎 我们可以谈谈
Tasha, we can talk about this.
他们想杀我
They were gonna kill me.
你却要保护他们
And now you're protecting them?
不 我是在保护你
No. I'm protecting you.
我很好 谢谢了
Yeah. I'm good. Thanks.
我们这么办
So here's how it's gonna be.
你要么走 要么加入我们
You can walk away or you can join my pack.
我不走
I'm not walking away.
那就证明你有资格留下
Then prove you got what it takes.
把他的心掏出来吃了
Eat his heart out.
凯特
Kate.
你不必这么做
You don't have to do this.
没人跟你说话 傻大个
No one's talking to you, Paul Bunyan.
怎么样
So?
不行
No.
带走他们 尽情玩
Take them. Have some fun.
给我打包一个心脏
Oh, and I want a heart to-go.
放在食物袋里
Put it in a doggie bag.
跪下
On your knees!
我真是受宠…
Wow. Well, I'm awfully flat…uhh!
小塔 我可以帮你好起来
T., I can help you get better.
我已经好了
Oh, I am better.
而且更聪明更强壮更厉害了
And smarter and stronger and awesome.
我就是一个超级英雄
I'm a freakin' superhero.
一个滥杀无辜的超级英雄吗
Who kills innocent people?
不 你不是这样的
No, that's not you.
你曾是个好孩子
You were a good kid.
我那时软弱 害怕
I was weak and scared.
我允许别人欺负我
I let people walk all over me …
妈妈 爸爸 朋友 男朋友
Mom, dad, friends, boyfriends,
还有你
you.
但我现在不再软弱了
But I'm not weak anymore.
我不再害怕了
And I'm not scared.
我令别人害怕
I'm scary.
我是想再给你一次机会
I was trying to give you a second chance.
你不会很…正常
You wouldn't have been… normal,
但我们可以拥有彼此
but we would've had each other.
我们依旧可以啊
We still can.
但我不会逃一辈子
But I'm not gonna spend my life on the run.
躲避外面那俩兄弟那样的人
from people like Mary-Kate and Ashley out there.
我们很强壮 凯特
We're strong, Kate.
我们想去哪都行
We can go anywhere we want.
想做什么都行
We do anything we want.
如果任何人妨碍我们…
And of anyone gets in our way…
你不用再孤身一人了
You don't have to be alone anymore.
我们可以一起走
We can do this together.
你没事吧
You okay?
不怎么样
I've been better.
这些人 真是难以置信
These guys, huh? Can you believe 'em?
是啊 就是几个小罗罗
Yeah, a couple of minor leaguers.
你死定了 没资格说话
You're dead. You don't get to talk.
实际上…
In fact…
让你们见识见识大佬 小子们
Well, welcome to the majors, boys.
凯特
Kate…
我们会很好的 好吗
We're gonna be good, okay?
我们会很棒的
We're gonna be great.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我们去追她吗
So we going after her?
我不知道 迪恩
I don't know, Dean.
你得承认 到了关键时刻
But you gotta admit, when push came to kill,
她做得很好
she did good.
是啊
Yeah.
也许你没有开枪打死她是件好事
So maybe it's a good thing you didn't shoot her.
真的吗 你要打这个马后炮
Really? You're gonna monday morning quarterback this thing?
如果你有什么牢骚要发
If you got an itch to scratch…
迪恩 我们俩都急着想办这案子
Dean, look, we both jumped on this case.
我同意 都有责任
I agree. Equal parts blame there.
但保持低调的目的是为了休息
But the whole idea behind laying low was to rest,
试着解决一切我们…
to…try and deal with everything we …
一切你所经历的事情
Everything you went through.
也许我们回归得太早了
Maybe we jumped back in too fast.
迪恩 你做了一阵恶魔啊
I mean, Dean, you were a demon.
血印还在
You still have the mark.
难道你就不想聊聊这事吗
Didn't you ever wanna talk about it?
聊聊 怎么聊
Talk about it? Talk about it how?
- 说吧 - 我说了 萨姆
- Come on, man. - I am coming on, Sam.
我知道发生了什么
Look, I know what happened.
好吗 我在的 记得吗
Okay? I was there. Remember?
我并不是想蒙混过去 我只是
I'm not trying to get by it. I just…
不是这样的
That's not what this was about.
那是哪样的
Then what is this about?
我是想重回正轨 明白吗
About gettin' back in the saddle. Okay?
做些好事 而不是沉浸在我的屁事里
Doing something good, not stewing in my own crap.
如果你还没准备好呢
And what if you're not ready?
我得承认
Well, I'll give you one thing.
你真擅长逃跑
Pretty damned good at getaways.
是啊
Yeah.
我认定活着要比死了强
Well, I decided that living was better than being dead.
不管怎样 谢谢你
For what it's worth, thank you.
毕竟她是你妹妹
At the end of the day, she was your sister.
不 她不是
No. She wasn't.
听我说 凯特
Listen to me, Kate.
你继续生活 不惹事
You keep moving, keep your nose clean,
我们就不必这样见面了
and we can stop meeting like this.
知道了
I hear ya.
我会的
And I will,
但我不能保证 因为…
but I'm not gonna promise, 'cause…
好
Yeah.
再见了 孩子
See you around, kid.
我真心希望不要再见
I sure as hell hope not.
假设你说得对
Let's say you're right.
- 说对什么 - 所有事
- About what? - Everything.
也许我还没准备好去猎魔
Maybe I'm not ready to hunt.
但我只是在努力做正确的事
But I am just trying to do the right thing, man,
因为我受够了做错事
'cause I'm so sick and tired of doing the wrong one.